(Leonard:)They find themselves, through no fault
of their own, you know, kind of addicted.
(Penny:)Yeah, get to the point.
I'm about to level up here.
(Leonard:)If a person doesn't have a sense
of achievement in their real life...
...it's easy to lose themselves in a world
where a false sense of accomplishment...
(Penny:)Yeah, jabber, jabber, jabber.
Okay, boys, Queen Penelope's back online.
(Leonard:)Penny, you've got...
(Leonard:)...Cheetos in your hair.
(Penny(pulling cheeto out of hair):)Oh, thanks.
(Leonard:)Wow.
LEONARD:
Hey, Penny, it's me again, Leonard.
PENNY:
Leonard, I said, not now.
LEONARD: I'm just a little concerned
about you and...
PENNY:
I said, not now.
LEONARD:
Okay, maybe later.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Hey, what's with him?
- Penny's been keeping him up at night.